我叫巴里·艾伦
My name is Barry Allen,
是现今世上速度最快的人
and I am the fastest man alive.
在外人看来  我只是个普通的鉴证专员
To the outside world, I'm an ordinary forensic scientist,
但在尖端科研实验室的朋友们的帮助下
but secretly, with the help of my friends at S.T.A.R. Labs,
我秘密地打击犯罪  寻找跟我一样的超能力者
I fight crime and find other meta-humans like me.
我让杀害母亲的凶手自食其果
I hunted down the man who killed my mother,
但我们的世界也因此出现了新的威胁
but in doing so, I opened up our world to new threats,
我是唯一来得及阻止他们的人
And I am the only one fast enough to stop them.
我叫闪电侠
I am The Flash.
《闪电侠》前情回顾
Previously on "The Flash"...
我们已经把乌龟人关起来了
We've got Turtle locked up in the pipeline.
现在要做的就是想个办法
All we got to do is use him to figure out
偷走极速的速度
how to steal Zoom's speed.
时间估计比我们想像的要长
That might take longer than we thought.
-为什么  -因为乌龟人死了
- Why's that? - Because Turtle's dead.
你所需要的就是搞清楚什么能触发你的震波
You need to figure out what triggers your vibes.
有时是当我
Sometimes it's when I touch something
触碰到和缺口有关的东西
that belongs to a breacher;
有时就这么发生了
sometimes it just happens.
事出必有因
There's always a cause.
我们要帮你救出杰西
We're gonna help you save Jesse.
你要我放弃在这里的一切吗
You want me to leave everything I have here?
我的生活
I mean, my life--
你在这不再有生活可言
You don't have a life here anymore.
极速太强大了
Zoom is too powerful.
关了它  快关了它
Close it. Close it now.
不
No!
杰伊没有白白死去
Jay's death was not in vain.
我们会再次见到极速
We will meet Zoom again,
等到那时  我会打败他
and the next time, I will beat him,
无论他是何方神圣
whoever that monster is.
地图上看着没这么深
It didn't look this deep on the map.
因为地图上的是平面图
That's 'cause maps are flat.
看着有三百多米深
This is, like, 1,000 feet deep.
你想要变得更快
Well, you want to get faster.
垂直摔下去估计能给你动力
Maybe plummeting to your death is the motivation you need.
要达到逃逸速度
So to reach escape velocity,
你得能跑
you're gonna have to go...
这么快
that fast.
我敢肯定达不到这速度
Well, that fast is impossible. I can promise you that.
"除了死亡  人生没有肯定的事"
"Nothing in life is promised except death"
埃德加·爱伦·坡
Edgar Allan Poe?
坎耶·韦斯特
Kanye West.
这个故事或许能让你好受些
If it makes you feel any better,
埃维尔·克尼维尔[冒险运动家]
Evel Knievel cleared a line of cars
根本没有超能力
that was twice this long,
还越过了一排两倍这么长的车队
and he didn't even have superpowers,
除非你骑着他那辆酷炫的摩托车
unless you count that sweet-ass ride.
你在说什么
Do you hear yourself?
什么  听着  你会没事的
What? Look, you're gonna be fine.
我有百分之八十的把握
I'm 80% sure of it.
-好  -百分之七十六
- Okay. - 76.
绝对有百分之七十二
Like, a strong 72.
停不下来了  凯特琳  帮我
I can't stop, Caitlin, help.
你要是没准备好  那最好就此打住
If you don't feel ready, you probably shouldn't do it.
并没帮上忙
Not helpful.
还没抓住极速
Look, Zoom's still out there.
只要找到了回到地球二的办法
And once I find a way back to Earth-2,
那我就必须比他快
I have to be faster than him.
我是说  现在
And, I mean, right now--
我的速度连杰伊都救不了
I wasn't even fast enough to save Jay.
我必须试试
I have to try.
他快成功了
He's gonna make it.
-不  -糟糕
- No! - Oh, damn.
"你干嘛还带着无人机  西斯科"
"Why'd you have to bring those drones along, Cisco"
"我也不知道"  不客气  各位
"Oh, I don't know." You're welcome, everyone.
签约项目  包括发行个人专辑
Signed projects, including releases of solo albums.
碧昂丝离开之后
Pop music would never be the same
天命真女的作品将就此改变
after Beyonce  left Destiny's Child.
慢着  这不对啊
Wait, that doesn't make any sense.
他们说的是参议员诺尔斯吗
They mean Senator Knowles?
让开
Scooch.
怎么了
What?
怎么样
So how'd it go?
他没有变成红贴纸贴在山上
Well, he's not a red splat on the side of a mountain.
咱们现在就这么定义成功
That's our new definition of success?
定义之一
It's one of them.
你没跳过峡谷吗
So, you didn't make the canyon jump?
没有  还有什么办法
No. What else can we try?
更大的峡谷
A bigger canyon?
好了  不跳峡谷了
Okay, fine, no more canyons.
我知道我能做到
I know I can crack this.
只是我方法不对
I've just been going about it wrong.
我得调整到最好状态
I need to find my leg up.
我们考虑阻力了吗
Have we factored in drag?
威尔斯  能再模拟一次吗
Wells, can we rerun the simulation?
暂时先别想了
Let it go for now.
我们还没抓到极速
Zoom's still out there.
他使整个世界  你们的世界陷入恐慌
He's terrorizing a whole world full of people, your world.
我这不是在闹着玩
You know, I'm not doing this for fun.
巴里  这一周我们都在忙这事
Barry, we've been working on this all week.
你累了  我们也累了
You're tired, we're tired.
是啊  我们需要停工休息一下
Yeah, what we need is some downtime.
停工期有助提高未来生产率
Downtime leads to increased productivity,
所以我们要出去玩
ergo we have to have fun.
而出去玩最好的方式
And the best way to have fun
就是一起去夜店玩
is for us to go out to the club.
我说得对吗  队友们
Am I right, team Flash?
嗨起来
Let's get turnt!
说真的  我们需要休息一下
No, but seriously, we need a break.
我觉得西斯科说得对
You know, I think Cisco's right,
连我都说我们该休息
and if I'm saying we need a break,
我们就真的该休息了
then you know it's serious.
好吧  那我们今晚出去玩
All right, let's go out tonight.
好啊  我可以去吗
Oh, yeah. Can I go?
除非我死了
Over my dead body.
你可以整天都泡在实验室里
Look, just 'cause you're stuck in this lab all day,
不代表我也要这样
doesn't mean I should be too.
等我入土了
Over my rotting corpse.
说好的尝试新事物
Look, what happened to trying new things,
认识新朋友呢
meeting new people?
你要我在这里开始新生活  不是吗
You said I should start a life here, right?
而且极速在那边  我们在这边
And Zoom's over there, and we're over here,
没有什么可担心的
so there's nothing to worry about.
总有可以担心的事
There's always something to worry about.
好吧  你说巴里他们是好人
Okay, well, you said Barry and them are good people
我应该多去了解他们
and I should get to know them.
我有说过
I did.
是啊
Yeah.
你知道他们无论如何都会保护我的安全
And you know they'll keep me safe no matter what.
我要有自己的生活  爸爸
Look, I have a life to live, dad,
我想去看看这个世界  求你了
and whole world to explore. Please?
求你了
Please?
好吧
Fine.
如果你要去  就要带上保护措施
But if you're gonna go, you should take protection.
爸爸
Oh, dad,
我不需要  我不知道你以为
I don't need--I don't know what you thought
我会去干嘛  但我
I was gonna be doing, but I...
好吧
Oh, right.
真的有必要吗  这有点...
I mean, is it necessary? It's kind of, you know...
不然我给你造个监狱方块
Or I could always build you an inescapable daughter cube.
好好笑啊
Funny.
但你知道我会逃出去的  对吧
You know I'd get out though, right?
好吧  那我戴着它
All right, fine. I'll do it.
谢谢
Thank you.
天呐  对不起  它老是响
Oh, god, sorry. It keeps doing that.
我爸非让我戴着它
My dad made me wear it.
别担心  没事的
Don't worry about it. It's all good.
我很高兴你来了  杰西
I'm really glad you came, Jesse,
虽然这里不怎么样
even though this place is less than ideal.
祝杯酒吧
Hey, toast?
敬杰伊
To Jay.
我在想如果杰伊在的话  他会说什么
I wonder what Jay would say if he was here right now.
神风特工队是什么
"What's a Kamikaze"
然后你会花十分钟跟他解释
and then you'd spend ten minutes explaining it.
然后他会说"开玩笑的  地球二上也有"
And he'd say, "Just kidding. We have those on earth-2."
好吧  我们没有那个  所以
Yeah, well, we don't have those, so...
抱歉  未成年小姐
I'm sorry, Miss Underage.
今晚我们谁也不想被你爸杀掉
None of us plan on getting murdered by your father tonight.
没事的  他就是嘴皮子厉害
Oh, whatever, he's all talk.
伙计们  你们好吗
Yo, guys, what's up?
很高兴你能来
Glad you could make it.
你好吗  沃利
What's up, Wally?
地方选得很有意思
Hey, interesting choice of venue.
井字游戏的主题很酷
The tic-tac-toe theme is cool.
-是巴里选的  -是西斯科选的
- Barry picked it. - Cisco picked it.
-我没  -真的吗
- I-- - For real?
对  是我选的  我不怎么出来玩
Yeah, I picked it. I don't go out much.
这家在点评网上有四颗星  所以
It had four stars on yelp, so...
好吧  有道理
Okay, fair enough.
所以这是谁
So who's this?
这是沃利  他是我的
This is Wally. He's my...
养父  或者继  收养
Foster, or step--adopted...
我的新  这是  他是我新认识的朋友
my new--this is-- he's my new friend.
这是杰西
This is Jesse.
杰西  你刚来这镇上吗
So, Jesse, are you new in town?
是  可以这么说
Yeah, you could say that.
我也是  你是从很远的地方来的吗
Yeah, me too. Are you from far away?
远得让你不敢相信
Like you wouldn't believe.
这样吧  我可以失陪一下吗
You know what? Would you just excuse me?
我得去化妆间整理一下我的  手表
I just need to go powder my...watch.
我知道我基本上算是你弟弟
Hey, so I know I'm practically your brother,
而且我只有杰伊个头的一半
and I'm, like, half Jay's size,
但你可以陪我跳舞吗
but you want to dance?
-当然  -来吧  我们走
- Sure. - Come on, let's go.
蠢手表
Stupid watch.
好的  伙计  你响够了吧
All right, buddy, you have beeped your last beep.
因此我会
Something else rising also,
用我邪恶的本能
some dark instinct about what I would do
对带走你的人
to the person who had taken you,
做出一些事
the things I would do.
最近沃利怎么样
So how's Wally doing?
他很好  他就是埋头学习
Yeah, he's good; he's just diving into his schoolwork.
-那很好  -是啊
- Good. - Yeah.
我很高兴
I'm glad.
天哪
Oh, God.
向我保证  如果我们真的结婚了
Promise me if we ever do get married,
你一定不要在我们的婚礼上跳这种舞
you will not do that dance at our wedding.
这我肯定能保证
Oh, I can promise you that.
我指的不是婚礼  是那种舞
I mean, not the wedding, the dancing.
怎么了
What?
我不知道  我只是觉得的
I don't know; I just think it's weird
我们在未来和地球二结婚很奇怪
that were married in the future and on earth-2.
我好奇咱们结婚了的二重身今晚在做什么
I wonder what our married doppelgangers are doing tonight.
大概是地球二版本的"聚一聚刷刷剧"
Probably earth-2's equivalent of "Netflix and chill."
听起来不错  我是说  对他们来说
Sounds nice. I mean, for them.
是闪电侠
It was the Flash!
我的钱包不见了
My wallet's gone.
有人拿走了我的手袋
Someone took my purse.
你又是谁
Who the hell are you?
好的  我知道了  谢谢了
Okay, I got it. Thanks, man.
抱歉
Hey, excuse me.
昨晚怎么回事
What happened last night?
我知道你没有抢劫那些人
I know you didn't rob these people.
我觉得无聊  所以想找点乐子
No, I was bored. Thought I'd have some fun.
这个人在六分钟之内
Well, look, whoever did this, they got everyone
把十个街区内的所有人都抢了
within a ten-block radius in under six minutes.
你没追上这个人吗
You couldn't catch them?
没有  这个极速者好像比我快
No, this speedster's faster than me, I guess.
难以置信
Unbelievable.
宝贝
Hey, babe.
我和那边的女孩谈过了
Hey, so I spoke to that girl over there.
她拍下了这张红色幻影的照片
She snapped a photo of the red blur.
看着熟悉吗
Look familiar?
这可不妙
This is not good.
我知道  这照片看起来和我
I know, it looks exactly like the photo
去年给你拍的那张一模一样
I took of you last year.
别担心  我们会想办法解决的
Don't worry, we'll figure it out.
我们总能想出办法
We always do.
是工作  我得走了
Oh, it's work. I've got to go.
随时通知我进展  好吗
Keep me posted, okay?
乔  我不想让人们把闪电侠
Joe, I don't want people thinking the Flash
当成小窃贼
is a petty thief.
我们得赶紧开始粉碎那些谣传
Well, we need to get to work squashing those rumors
以免它们散播
before they spread.
这就是了  伙计们
Here it is, people:
闪电侠变坏了的证据
evidence that the Flash has gone rogue.
会不会是那个戴钢盔的极速者
Couldn't it be the speedster in the helmet?
这张照片就能说明
The photo speaks for itself.
没有头盔的反光
No helmet glare,
证明这就是红色极速者
confirming that this is the scarlet speedster.
我们要揭露他的谎言
We're gonna expose him as a fraud.
麦凯  我要你去警察局
Mckay, I want you at the police department
尽可能多地采访
getting any interview you can.
好的  马上办
Okay, on it.
威廉姆斯  目击证人采访
Williams, eyewitness encounters.
这座城市的民众需要知道
The people of this city need to know
被一个英雄打劫是什么感觉
what it feels like to be robbed by a hero.
韦斯特  我想要你以自己看到的写篇文章
West, I want you to do a piece on it from your perspective.
你昨晚在现场  你看到亲眼看到他了
You were there last night. You've seen him in action.
好吧  但是为什么闪电侠想要
Okay, but why would the Flash need to make off
抢那几百块钱
with a couple of hundred bucks
他可是救过那么多人
when he's saved so many lives?
我是说  他是个真正的英雄
I mean, he is actually a hero.
艾瑞丝  你是个聪明的女人  别这么天真
Iris, you're a smart woman. You can't be that naive.
我们住在一个充满超能力者的城市里
We live in a city full of meta-humans
他们一直为所欲为
who continually do whatever they want,
闪电侠也是其中之一
The Flash included.
写出来吧
Write it up,
他从英雄堕落成了坏蛋
his journey from streak to freak,
明天放到我桌上
Due on my desk tomorrow.
怎么样  昨晚玩得好吗
So... fun night?
在那混乱发生之前
Before all the chaos broke loose?
我会不惜一切
Then I would do anything
也要把你救回来
to get you back,
包括杀死一个人
Including killing a man.
告诉我是我听错了
Tell me I'm not hearing this right.
不  你没听错
No, that's true.
极速抓了你
Zoom had you.
极速需要闪电侠的速度
Zoom needed the Flash's speed.
不是他就是你
And it was him or you.
而我不想失去你
And I was not going to lose you.
你知道  你是我的英雄
You know, you were my hero.
我父亲  天才科学家
My dad, the brilliant scientist
只要有心就可以达成任何事
who could accomplish anything he put his mind to.
他教导我梦想没有界限
He taught me I could never dream too big.
但现在
But now...
现在你成了杀人凶手
now you're a killer,
我几乎不认识你了
and I barely recognize you at all.
-杰西  -别别别
- Jesse - No, no, no.
别担心
Don't-don't worry.
我不会离开太远
I'm not going far.
我说  那个极速者究竟哪里来的
I mean, where did this speedster even come from?
我不知道  老兄
I don't know, man.
我只知道那团幻影把我弄得晕头转向
All I know is that blur made 60 smackeroos off of me.
难以置信
Ridiculous.
可能又是极速的手下
Maybe it's another one of Zoom's henchmen somehow?
缺口都关闭了
The breaches are closed.
只有通过粒子加速器爆炸
The only other way to become a speedster
才能成为极速者
is from a particle accelerator explosion.
好吧  那为什么现在才曝光你自己
Okay, but then why only make yourself known now?
明白我在说什么吧
You see what I'm saying?
我们之前肯定会见过他们行动
We'd have had to seen them in action before.
我不是在说这话解释得通  我只是在说
I'm not saying it makes sense; I'm just saying
这是成为极速者的唯一办法
that's the only other way to become a speedster.
其实还有别的办法
Actually, there's another way.
这叫终极速度-9
It's called Velocity-9.
这名字太性感了  是干什么
That's a sexy-ass name. What is it?
这是种神速药
It's a speed drug.
你在地球二时  杰伊使用它
Jay took it when you were on Earth-2
来从超能力者手中保护了城市
to save the city from a Meta-human.
什么  你怎么没跟我说这件事
What? How could you not tell me this?
我答应过杰伊不会说
I promised Jay I wouldn't.
杰伊  你怎么...为什么
Jay, what do you-- why?
因为  杰伊知道这药的危险性
Because Jay knew how dangerous this drug is.
我也知道  巴里
I should know, Barry;
是斯诺和我一起研发的
Snow and I worked on it together.
伙计们  我一直在全力以赴应战
Guys, I have been busting my butt out there,
挑战自己的极限
pushing myself to the limit,
想要变得更强  想要速度更快
trying to get better, trying to be faster,
而你们现在告诉我  一直以来
and you're telling me that there's been something
有这么一种东西可以帮助我
this whole time that could've helped me?
这药能帮我打倒极速
This could've helped me take down Zoom.
能帮我拯救地球二的乔  拯救杰伊
It could have helped me save Earth-2 Joe, save Jay.
杰伊病了
Jay was sick.
他服下的那药物  在恢复速度的同时
The drug that he took to regain his speed
还会导致细胞退化
was also causing cellular degeneration.
它在慢慢的杀死他
It was killing him.
我尽力帮他  我尽力找出解药
I tried to help, I tried to find a cure,
但以我的经验来看  影响只是暂时的
But in all my experiments, the effects were just temporary.
终极速度-9是致命的
The V-9 is deadly.
为什么不告诉我  为什么瞒着我
Why not tell me this? Why keep me in the dark?
凯特琳
Caitlin.
我在哪
Where am I?
-你没事吧  -你感受到震波了吗
- Are you okay? - Did you vibe?
社交网络
是超能力者
Meta-human.
社交网络软件成功了
Yeah, social media app for the win.
坏蛋闪电侠回来了
Bad Flash is back.
坏蛋闪电侠  什么
Bad Flash... what?
不  我失去起名能力了
No. I'm losing my touch over here.
他就快到第五街和埃弗里特街口
He's coming up on Fifth and Everett.
你可以抄小巷拦截他
You can use the alley to cut him off.
女极速者
A lady speedster?
虽然只花了两年  但是终于出现了
It only took us two years, but we finally got one,
一个女极速者
a lady speedster.
有个问题问你  纯粹科学方面的
Hey, here's a question for you, purely scientific,
她长得漂亮吗
was she good-looking?
我当时正处于挨打状态呢
You know, I was a little busy getting my ass handed to me,
所以真没怎么留意
so I didn't really notice.
对对对  但是你知道
Right, right, right, but, you know,
下一次  为了科学研究
next time, for science?
行啊  下次她打我脸的时候
Okay, yeah, next time she punches me in the face,
我会确保先要到她的电话号码的
I'll be sure to get her number.
这就对了
There you go.
但是问题还没解决  她是什么人
But the question remains, who is she?
不知道
I have no idea.
我们可以用面部识别软件来查查
We could run her through the facial recognition.
她戴着面具
She had a mask on.
她的战衣是怎么样的
What was her suit like?
这问题很有价值
Hey, it's a valid question.
没错  她的战衣是怎么个构造
It is, actually. How was her suit constructed?
很不错  非常好
It was good. It was very good.
跟我的一样
It was like mine.
制作它的那个人
It was made by somebody
非常熟悉极速者的需要
who understands the needs of a Speedster.
所以是某个可以接触到科技和实验室的人
So that would be someone with access to tech and a lab.
不  我有一个很不好的想法
Oh, no. I'm having a very bad thought.
在我设计终极速度-9时
When I designed V-9,
我没法解决格式化细胞外基质的问题
I was having trouble formatting the extracellular matrix,
所以我找到了水星实验室的旧同事
so I called a colleague of mine at Mercury Labs
寻求一些援助  伊丽莎·哈蒙
for some assistance, Eliza Harmon.
她知道如何研制这个神速药吗
She knows how to make this speed drug?
不知道  我遵守了
No, I followed the protocols
信息划分的规定
of information compartmentalization.
终极速度-9的必要结构  我只告诉了她
I only gave her three of the eight components
八种成分中的三种
necessary for V-9's structure.
所以她不知道完整的配方
Okay, so she didn't have the full recipe.
除非她逆向还原出了她自己的终极速度-9
Unless she reverse engineered her own V-9.
伊丽莎是个天才  但是这样做太不像她了
Eliza's a genius, but that's way out of character for her.
值得一探究竟
Well, it's worth taking a look.
我去见见她
I'll go see her.
我也一起去
Hey, I'm coming too.
这下好了
Great.
我去训练了
I'm gonna go train.
水星实验室
打扰了
Knock-knock.
我出现幻觉了吗  还是这真是失宠了的
Am I hallucinating, or is that disgraced
水星前任职员凯特琳·斯诺
ex-Mercury employee Caitlin Snow?
伊丽莎·哈蒙  熬夜做研究
Eliza Harmon, burning the midnight oil.
你不需要休息一下吗
Don't you ever take a break?
你知道吗
Well, you know what they say,
硫氰酸根离子不会自己结合在一起
these thiocyanate ions won't bond themselves.
你这位英俊的朋友怎么称呼
Who is your handsome friend?
乔·韦斯特警探  女士你好
Detective Joe West, ma'am.
是个警探啊
Detective?
您怎么大驾光临了
What brings you around these parts?
说来有趣
Well, that's a funny story.
你知道有个极速者
You know how there's a speedster
在肆虐这座城市吗
that's been wreaking havoc on the city?
我听说闪电侠发疯了
Yeah, I heard the Flash went nuts.
人出名后难免会这样
Fame will do it to you.
他无法接受成为众人注目的中心
I guess some people can't handle the limelight, right?
但我们知道其实另有其人
Well, we happen to know it was someone else.
所以我们才来这里调查这件事
That's why we're here looking into this.
你真有《法律与秩序》的精神  凯特琳
Wow, how very "Law & Order" of you, Caitlin.
你记得几个月前
Do you remember that formula
我找你帮我处理的那个配方吗
that you were helping me with a few months ago?
隐约记得
Yeah, vaguely.
就是这个配方牵涉其中
We think that it was somehow involved.
怎么会  那是什么配方
How? What did you have me working on?
这是机密
It's classified,
我只能说这是种增强剂
but let's just say it was some kind of enhancement,
我们担心我的研究被偷走了
and we're afraid that my research was stolen.
不是在这个实验室被偷的
Not from this lab.
好吧  别传出去  这里挺松垮的
Okay, between you and me, the place is pretty vulnerable.
自从几个月前被闯入之后
Ever since that break-in a few months ago,
我们有些人认为麦吉没有充分地
some of us think Mcgee hasn't sufficiently
加强保安
stepped up security,
但我的研究都有锁好
but I kept my research on lock
我在交回给你前把原样本都销毁了
and destroyed the originals when it was given back to you.
但你可以随意搜查我的实验室
But hey, you're free to look around my lab if you want.
我认为不需要这么做
I don't think that'll be necessary.
抱歉  我希望我能帮到你
Sorry. I wish I could be more help.
没事  这其实也让我松了一口气
It's okay. It's actually kind of a relief.
如果你有任何线索就打给我  好吗
Will you call me if you hear anything, though?
没问题  这是朋友该做的事
Of course. That's what friends are for.
谢谢
Thank you.
你怎么看
So what do you think?
我们暂时相信她
For now, we take her at her word.
韦斯特  你的文章写得咋样了
West, how's your article coming?
挺好的
Um, great.
我的线人确切地知道
I have a source who knows for a fact
这个极速者不是闪电侠
that this speedster is not the Flash
而是假冒的
but an imposter.
你的线人是谁
Ah, who's your source?
我不能说出来
I am not at liberty to say.
如果你不能说你的线人是谁
Well, if you can't tell me your source,
那我就按原来的报道发了
I'm running the original story.
等一下  等一下
Wait, wait, wait.
你是对的  一个匿名线人
You're right; what's one unnamed source
怎么能跟几十个目击者比呢
compared to dozens of eyewitnesses?
其实  我在努力绞尽脑汁
Honestly, I'm just-- I'm having a hard time
围绕着你的视角写这篇报道
wrapping my head around your vision for the story.
只是有些内容还理不清
Something isn't adding up.
我们深入探讨一下吧
How about we talk about it some more?
一起喝咖啡探讨  怎么样
Grab some coffee? What you say?
现在去喝咖啡
Coffee? Right now?
没错  没错
Yeah, yeah.
摄入一点咖啡因应该不会伤身吧
I mean, a little caffeine never hurt anybody, right?
当然不会
Sure.
我好累
I'm so tired.
你逼自己逼得太狠了
Oh, well, you've been pushing yourself too hard.
不  不够狠
No, not hard enough.
我已经受够总是被忽视
I'm sick of always being passed over
不被认可  无法晋升
for the grant, for the promotion.
我的报酬过低  人手不足
I'm underpaid and understaffed
我的研究进度已经落后半年了
and six months behind on my research.
所以我才会开始搞这个
That's why I started all of this.
你的问题在于你太追求完美了
Your problem is you're too much of a perfectionist.
你不需要这样  混乱中也有美
You don't have to be. There's beauty in chaos.
我可没时间混乱
I don't have time for chaos.
这本来能改善事物
This was supposed to fix things,
结果却把事物变得更糟
and it ended up making it worse.
傻姑娘
Oh, silly girl.
你知道它能让你舒缓压力心情舒畅
You know it makes you feel better to blow off some steam.
你为达目的不择手段
You will say anything for a fix.
我们被怀疑都是你的错
It's your fault we're hooked.
是凯特琳的错
It's Caitlin's fault;
如果她不想让我们知道她的研究
if she didn't want us to find out what she was working on,
她就不该轻易交到我们手上
she shouldn't have made it so damn easy.
这不够我们两个人服用
There's not enough for both of us.
我们要留来应急
We--we need to save it for an emergency.
你现在服用  之后再想怎么弄更多
You take it now; worry about getting more later.
你会感谢我的
You'll thank me.
我知道怎么对我们最好  怎么拿到更多
I know what's best for us and where to get more.
你在干什么
Whatcha doing?
-训练  -训练
- Training. - Training?
艾伦  别傻了
Allen, don't be stupid.
我知道你拿走了V9  艾伦
I know you took the V-9, Allen.
-不  我没有  -没有吗
- No, I haven't. - Oh, no?
没有
No.
我拿了  但是还没有用
I took it, but I haven't taken it yet.
-很好  -告诉我为什么不能用
- Good. - Tell me why I shouldn't.
自己想明白
Figure it out.
如果游戏已经被操纵了
If the game is already rigged,
我为什么不能让它公平一点
why can't I level the playing field?
如果所有人都在作弊
I mean, if everybody else is cheating,
那我...我想提高速度
how can-- I want to be fast enough
去阻止极速和其他极速者伤害我的朋友
to stop Zoom and any speedster that tries to hurt my friends.
我难道不该竭尽全力吗
Shouldn't I use everything in my power to do that?
你想走捷径  对不对
You want to take a shortcut; is that right?
你想走捷径吗  记好了
You want to take a shortcut? Remember this.
每当你向你的原则妥协一次
You lose a chunk of your humanity
你就会失去一些人性
every time you compromise your values.
抱歉  这话居然能从你嘴里说出来
Sorry, that's really good coming from you.
那就别像我一样
So don't be like me.
做个更好的人
Be better.
像杰伊一样
Be like Jay.
你还好吗
Are you okay?
我还好
Oh, yeah, I'm fine.
排除伊丽莎的嫌疑后
Hey, any luck locating our speedster
我们有极速者的其他线索吗
since Eliza checked out?
我还在找  不过
I'm still working on it, but...
是时候找点乐子了
Time to have some fun.
西斯科  乔
Hey! Cisco! Hey,Joe!
她把我关在管道监狱里了
Hey, she's got me in the pipeline!
-你想怎样  -V9在哪  凯特琳
- What do you want? - Where's the V-9, Caity?
我需要升个级
I need a fix.
伊丽莎  是你吗
Eliza, is that you?
伊丽莎现在不在这里
Oh, Eliza's not here right now.
我叫弹道
My name is Trajectory.
为什么这些疯子总是给自己起外号
Oh, why do the crazy ones always name themselves?
伊莉莎  终极速度-9非常危险
Look, Eliza, Velocity-9 is very dangerous, okay?
我一个朋友因为它身体很不舒服
It made a friend of mine very sick,
而且他体内本身就有神速力
and he already had the Speed Force in him.
听着  你的细胞组织
Look, your cellular system--
够了
Enough!
你真是让我无聊透顶
You are boring me to death.
把终极速度给我
Hand over the V.
我是医生  我宣过誓的
I'm a physician. I took an oath.
我不能给你会伤害你的东西
I can't give you anything that will hurt you.
那好  要么把终极速度交出来
Right, so either hand over the V,
要么这个爱猫男去拿给我
or the cat guy gets it.
你  快去
Hey, move, now.
所有的药瓶都没有了
Look, all the flasks are gone.
现在什么都没有
There's nothing left.
我真的希望你们别逼我做
Hey, I was really hoping you wouldn't make me do
如果不交出我要的东西
one of those "I have to kill you each one by one
就一个个杀光这种事
until you give me what I want."
好吧
Oh, well.
等等
Wait.
你想要V9
You want V-9?
我们给你做
We'll make it for you.
爸爸  你不能这么做
Dad, you can't.
我们有所有的原料
We have all the ingredients.
我可没什么耐心  所以你最好动作快点
I'm not a patient person, so better move fast.
我的拿铁  你的闪电侠
Latte for me, and a Flash for you.
这家伙居然还有同名饮料
Wow, this guy even gets a drink named after him.
是呀  他拯救了很多条生命
Yes, he does; he's saved a lot of people's lives.
大家想表达一下自己的感激
They just want to show their appreciation.
要我说有点夸张了
A little too much, if you ask me.
为什么你总跟别人的看法不一样
Why can't you see what everyone else sees?
几年前  我因为调查报道了
A few years back, I won the Dornfeld Award
市长办公室的腐败情况
for investigative reporting
for my story on corruption in the mayor's office.
我调查了那个广受爱戴的人
I investigated a man that everyone loved.
那个市长年又上镜  还是个战争英雄
The mayor was young, telegenic, a former war hero.
他以压倒性的民众支持率当选市长
He was voted in with overwhelming popular support.
那真是
It was...
但我知道他的竞选有一个黑帮在背后
But--but I knew that his campaign was bought and paid for
出钱支持他
by the mob.
好吧  但不是所有人都像他一样
Okay, but not everyone is a corrupt mayor.
可我看到了其他人所看不到的他
But I saw him for what everyone else was too blind to see.
人人都想要一个英雄
Everyone wants a hero.
是  但闪电侠确实是个英雄
Yeah, but in this case, the Flash actually is one.
爱瑞丝  我们的工作
Iris, Iris, it's our job
就是确保民众  包括英雄
to ensure that people, even heroes,
为他们的言行负责
are held accountable for their actions.
那我猜
So I'm guessing
你的约会准则上面
on your list of dating pros and cons,
反对闪电侠的人一定是没机会了
being anti-Flash is a major dealbreaker.
约会准...
Dating pros and...
你觉得这是个...
Did you think that this...
什么  不是  不是
Oh, what? No, no.
不  你就当没听到  我懂
No, forget what I said. I get it.
你说想探讨一下这篇报道
You just wanted to talk about the story some more...
只是为了拖延
to stall.
是啊  因为你也不想
Right, because you're trying to get out
写这篇文章
of writing this article altogether.
斯科特  等等  别走
Scott, wait, please don't leave.
我很抱歉  我不知道这是...
I'm sorry, I didn't know that this was...
你怎么会知道呢
Why would you?
我先走了
Excuse me.
这就是你要的东西
It's what you wanted.
现在放她走
Now let her go.
我怎么知道你们两个是不是
How do I know the two of you
在里面加镇定剂  好拿下我呢
didn't lace this with a sedative to put me on my ass?
我们不会那么做的
We wouldn't do that.
谨慎点总没错  对吧
You can never be too safe, right?
不要
No!
谢谢你的东西  斯诺
Thanks for the fix, Snow.
去找巴里  你没事吧
Get Barry. Are you okay?
你把牢房做得很坚固  西斯科
Well, good job on the cell, Cisco.
杰西
Jesse.
-发生什么了  -让她侧过去
- What happened? - Turn her on her side.
伊丽莎给她注射了V-9
Eliza shot her up with V-9.
她要休克了  药物含量太高了
She's going into shock. It's too pure.
别睡过去  杰西  别睡过去
Stay with me, Jesse. Stay with me.
我们该怎么做
What do we do?
我们得把她体内的V-9排出来
We've got to get the V-9 out of her system.
她需要输血
She needs a blood transfusion.
新的血液会把药物冲出来
The new blood will flush the drug out of her system.
-她是什么血型  -Pz阴性
- What blood type is she? - Pz negative.
伙计  这个地球上可没有这种血型
Yeah, that's not a thing on this Earth, man.
我有
I'm a match.
杰西
Jesse.
发生了什么
What happened?
我们  你没事了  你会好起来的
We-- you're fine. You're-- you're gonna be fine.
我们已经把你体内的药物排出来了
We got the drug out of your system.
看来你又挽救了大局
Looks like you saved the day again.
听我说  亲爱的  我知道这还不够
Look, honey, I know that this isn't enough.
不过  我向你保证
I promise you, though,
我一定会用我的下半辈子
I'm going to spend the rest of my life
为我做的那件可怕的事
making it up to you for the--
向你补偿的
for that terrible thing that I did.
-真的吗  -真的
- Yeah? - Yes.
那你为了保护我
And how many more terrible things
还会再做多少可怕的事呢
are you gonna do to protect me?
你这是什么意思
What does that mean?
你所做的每一件事
I mean, everything that you do
你为我做的每一件事
and everything that you have done for me,
都太阴暗了  你甚至都没明白
it's so dark, and-- and you don't even see it.
你刚才在那甚至都没有犹豫
I mean, you didn't even hesitate out there.
当然不会犹豫
Of course not.
我不能失去你  杰西
I'm not going to lose you, Jesse.
好吧  可是你连想都不想
Okay, but you just gave that crazy speedster
就给了那发疯的极速者所有想要的东西
everything she wanted without even blinking,
你都没有想过
without even thinking
其他人可能会因此有危险
what other lives could be at stake.
我的责任是保护你
It is my job to keep you safe,
保护你  这才是我要做的
to protect you, that's my job.
这才是重要的
That's all that matters.
或许不应该是
Well, maybe it shouldn't be.
凯特琳  我知道她是你的朋友
Caitlin, I know she was your friend and all,
可是这个乖乖女已经变坏
but homegirl has gone cuckoo bird.
她现在还有了更多V-9
Now she's out there with more V-9.
她不知道的是
What she doesn't know is,
我在药里放了微型追踪器
I put in micro tracker in the drug.
这个办法真高明
Hmm, that's a brilliant idea.
你跑得快  但是你无处可藏
You can run, but you can't hide.
这一切都怪我
I'm the one to blame for all this,
所以我得想办法弥补
So I need to help fix it.
要怪的人不是你  斯诺
There's plenty of blame to go around, Snow.
她在什么位置
What's her location?
弹道
位置追踪
中城大桥
Central City Bridge.
她为什么来回跑
Why is she running back and forth?
恶人在做恶了
Villains gonna vill.
她是在制造摩擦力
She's creating friction.
还是以这种震动和速度
And at that vibration and speed...
-怎么了  -彻底混乱
- What? - Complete chaos.
她会毁了大桥的
She could destroy that whole bridge.
还有桥上所有的人
And everyone on it.
各位  这座桥就要踏了
Guys, this bridge is coming down.
巴里  桥上现在大约有两百个人
Barry, there's about 200 people on that bridge right now.
你真是太扫兴了
You're ruining all my fun.
注意 桥要踏了
弹道太远了
Trajectory's too far away.
跑到河对岸也追不上她
You won't get to her running across the river.
跳过去的话就可以
I will if I jump.
巴里  想要跳过去的话
Barry, to make that jump,
你得达到每秒1122米
you'll need to go Mach 3.3,
但只能持续一秒钟
but only for a second.
好的
Okay.
太棒了  伙计
Yeah, buddy!
一切都结束了  伊丽莎
It's over, Eliza.
永远不会结束
It is never over.
等等
Wait!
别再注射了
Stop doing this to yourself.
其实你并不想伤害别人
You don't actually want to hurt anyone.
你一点也不了解我
You don't know anything about me.
对  但我知道你不是坏人
No, I know you're not a bad person.
是你体内的V-9在作祟
This is the V-9 in your system.
我明白你想当最棒的极速者的感受
I also know what it feels like to want to be the best.
你觉得没有足够的时间
It makes you feel like there's not enough time
好好完成事情
to accomplish things the right way,
但你这么做是在逃避
but it's a cop-out.
它会害死你
And this is killing you.
看看你自己  伊丽莎  你出状况了
Look at yourself, Eliza. You're not well.
请让我们帮你吧
Let us help you, please.
我只需要这些帮助
That is all the help I need.
我跑得比你快
How does it feel to know that I am faster
感觉怎么样
than you will ever be?
再见
See you around.
闪电变成蓝色了
The lightning, it's turning blue.
闪电侠阻止了邪恶的女极速者
你的文章写得很好
Your article was well-written.
谢谢
Thank you.
报道真相比较容易下笔
You know, it's a lot easier to write when it's the truth.
英雄不一定都是骗子
Not every hero is a fraud.
可以相信他们
It's okay to believe in them.
我已经知道了
So I've been told.
有时  就算很棒
And sometimes, even great journalists,
很聪明和很杰出的记者
smart and brilliant journalists,
也会搞错情况
can misread situations.
有时他们也会感到出乎意料
And sometimes they can be caught off guard.
那晚的事
Look, about the other night,
我有点意外
it--it just surprised me.
等我缓过来了  我...
But once the surprise went away, I, uh...
没有那种准则
not a dealbreaker.
我知道了
Noted.
好吧
Okay.
你看见杰西了吗
Hey, have you seen Jesse?
没有
No.
爸爸
Hey, dad.
是我
It's me.
多年来  你一直履行着
Listen, your job over the years
保护我免受伤害的责任
has been to shield me from harm.
现在  我要独自到外面的
But now it's my turn to go out into this new world
新世界去  不被保护
on my own, no shield,
探索这个地球
and discover what this earth can offer.
你是我最好的老师
You know, you are the best teacher I've ever had,
但我不知道你还能教我什么
but I don't know what more you can teach me.
我爱你
I love you.
请不要来找我
Please, don't come looking for me.
所以伊丽莎跑太快消失了
So Eliza just evaporated from running too fast?
好像是跟杰伊一样  细胞消退了
Looks like cellular degeneration, same as Jay's.
杰伊警告过我们V9很危险
Jay warned us V-9 was dangerous.
现在我们总算知道了
At least now we know why.
你找到杰西了吗
You find Jesse?
她离开了
She went out.
巴里  怎么了
Barry, what is it?
伊丽莎消失之前
It's just right before Eliza disappeared,
她的闪电变成蓝色
her lightning, it turned blue.
没错
Right.
如果这是V9的不良反应呢
What if it's a side effect of the V-9?
杰伊也用了终极速度-9
Yeah, but Jay took Velocity-9,
他的闪电没有变成蓝色
And his lightning didn't turn blue.
他能跑多快
About how fast was he running?
没有伊丽莎那么快
Not as fast as Eliza.
如果V9能产生蓝色闪电
All right, so what if V-9 is what turns your lightning blue?
极速比我快那么多就说得通了
I mean, that would explain why Zoom is so much faster than me.
若真如此  他肯定生病了
If that's true, then that means he's sick, right?
他要死了
He's dying.
所以他要你的速度
That's why he wants your speed.
他要死了  他需要治疗
He's dying, and he needs a cure.
跟杰伊一样
Same as jay.
不
No.
杰伊  不
Jay? No.
他在我们面前死去
See, he died right in front of us.
极速在我们面前杀死他
Zoom killed him right in front of us.
西斯科  我们见过极速者
Cisco, we've seen a speedster
同时出现在两个地方
be in two places at once before.
有个办法能找出真相
Then I guess there's one way to find out.
现在正好告诉你们
I guess now would be a good time
我一直震波看到极速
to tell you all I've been vibing Zoom.
什么
What?
你这样...多久了
You... for how long?
从关闭最好一个缺口开始
It started when we closed the last breach.
每次都是发生在我
And every time it's happened,
靠近那玩意儿的时候
I've been near that thing.
我们需要你震波
We need to know.
不
Oh, no.
不  不...
No, no...
西斯科...
Cisco...
你看见什么了
What did you see?
我看见杰伊了
I saw Jay.
他就是极速
He's Zoom.
巴里
Barry!